Downloaded from MoviesMod.at
In the next five days...
Muzan will come.
Use me as bait...
and cut off Muzan's head.
What makes you think that?
Just my intuition.
That's all.
No reason.
The other children... won't agree...
to using me as bait.
You're the only one that I can ask...
Gyomei.
Even if you behead him, he won't die.
The only thing that can destroy Muzan...
is most likely sunlight.
If he doesn't die even after
you've destroyed his head...
you'll be in...
for a drawn-out battle
until the sun rises.
Understood.
If that is your wish, Master.
Thank you.
Please...
don't let any more...
of my precious children die.
That is my wish.
So, you think you've
driven me into a corner?
You're all about to go straight to Hell!
You eyesore Demon Slayers!
Tonight, I'm going to massacre
every one of you!
You're the one who's going to Hell, Muzan!
You're not getting away, no matter what!
Do it, then!
Let's see you try...
Tanjiro Kamado!
I'll absolutely defeat you...
Muzan Kibutsuji!
What is this place?
Horizontally, vertically,
it's all messed up!
KILL
Was it built...
with an enemy's Blood Demon Art?
I don't know
what's going on around me...
but I know Ms. Tamayo
was holding Muzan down!
But...
who knows how long she can last?
Calm down, Kanroji!
R-Right!
Stay with me!
I've got to reach Muzan
as soon as possible and defeat him!
As soon as possible!
That's the bottom!
I'll be killed if I smash into it!
I'll use a move to change my trajectory
and find something to grab onto!
DESTROY
I'm off-balance!
The pressure of the fall
is keeping me from exerting myself!
DESTROYER
OF DEMONS
Mr. Gi--
Are you all right?
Yes!
Thank you very much!
You saved me--
Water Breathing...
First Form...
Water Surface Slash!
Tanjiro!
- Water Breathing...
Sixth Form...
Third Form...
Whirlpool!
Flowing Dance!
Mr. Giyu's too amazing.
He can tell from my slightest movement
which move I'm going to use.
Then he unleashes his own in a way
that keeps us from slashing each other.
He's unbelievable!
What's going on in his mind right now?
This must be...
that demon base Shinazugawa
and Iguro mentioned.
Meaning that...
Kibutsuji must've gathered us all here...
to wipe out the Hashira
and the Demon Slayer Corps.
From here on in,
we'll need to be even more vigilant.
Right!
- Let's go.
- Right!
Serpent Breathing...
Fifth Form...
Slithering Serpent!
Stay away from Kanroji...
you scums!
Mr. Iguro, you're so wonderful!
- Are you hurt?
- Not at all!
- Come on, then.
- Right!
Tokito!
That's a huge horde of demons.
Looks like they've been given
Lower Rank-level powers.
They're being used to try
and wear us down.
What about the Master?
He went on ahead of us.
It was a noble end.
The Master...
would never make a mistake
like allowing a demon to find him.
Did he use himself as bait?
That's right.
Because he didn't
have much longer to live.
Master...
When I was hovering...
between life and death...
after a demon attack...
the Master was there for me
the whole time.
He did the same for every Corps member...
in their final moments.
Like a father.
Yes. I know.
Muzan not only took my brother from me...
but our father, as well.
Damn him...
Muzan!
I'm going to torture him to death!
I'll show him what Hell looks like!
Don't worry.
We all feel the same way.
Master...
I couldn't protect you.
There's no end to you lowlifes.
Show me what you've got!
I'll kill every last one of you!
Comin'...
through!
More falling, huh?
I ended up in this crazy place
without any warning...
but there's a whole boatload of demons,
so it's the perfect place...
to test the results of my training!
What is this place?
Is it the demon headquarters?
Where are the others?
Big Brother...
Please be safe, too, Big Brother!
I just heard a sound.
He might be somewhere nearby!
I'll never forgive him!
No way...
am I ever going to forgive him!
It smells like blood.
What is this place?
Oh my, is someone here?
Wow, and you're a girl!
You look so young and tasty!
I'll have to thank Nakime for this later.
Shinobu...
Leave the Demon Slayer Corps.
I know you're trying hard.
You're really giving it your all...
but Shinobu, you'll probably...
I want you to be happy
like any normal girl...
and live on until you're elderly.
You've already...
done enough.
No!
No way am I quitting!
I'm going to avenge you
if it's the last thing I do!
Tell me!
What did the demon look like?
Which bastard got you?
Tell me, Big Sister!
Please!
I could never live a normal life
after someone did this to you!
Big Sister!
It was a demon...
who looked like he had
blood poured on his head.
Well, well...
nice to meet you!
My name is Doma.
What a wonderful night.
With a carefree smile on his face...
he speaks in a serene, gentle manner.
H-Help me...
Please help me!
Shh!
Can't you see that I'm talking?
Are you okay?
Wow! You're fast!
Are you a Hashira?
Oh, don't worry!
You can just leave her there.
I'll be sure to eat her later.
Upsy-daisy.
The weapons...
that demon wielded...
were a pair of sharp fans.
I'm the founder
of the Eternal Paradise Faith.
My job is to attain bliss
with all of my worshippers.
So, I'll be sure to pick
that girl clean, too.
This guy...
is the demon who killed my big sister.
Everyone's bliss?
How deluded are you?
This girl was unwilling
and crying out for help.
And isn't that why I saved her?
That girl's no longer suffering.
She's no longer in pain
and no longer in fear.
Everyone's afraid of death, you know.
So, I do them a favor by eating them.
They get to live on with me.
For all eternity!
To save my followers,
I take in their desires,
their blood and their flesh...
and guide them...
to ever greater heights.
You can't possibly be in your right mind.
Are you sure you're mentally intact?
You truly make me want to gag!
What?
We've only just met,
but you're being awfully hostile.
Oh! I see.
You poor thing.
You must've gone through
something unbearable.
I'd be happy to listen.
Go on, let it all out.
"Unbearable" barely even scratches
the surface!
The one who killed my big sister,
it was you!
Doesn't this haori ring a bell?
Huh?
Oh!
You mean that girl
who used Flower Breathing?
Such a gentle, sweet child!
The one I didn't get to devour
because the sun came up.
I remember her.
I sure wish I could've eaten her--
Insect Breathing...
Dance of the Bee Sting...
True Flutter!
What an astounding thrust!
I couldn't stop it with my hand!
Blood Demon Art...
Frozen Lotus.
It's freezing! The air's so cold,
it feels like it's ripping my lungs apart!
Oh, you sure are a quick one!
But too bad for you.
Thrusts can't kill a demon.
It's the neck.
You need to chop off the head.
DESTROY
I may not be able
to kill you with my thrusts...
but what about poison?
I'll find out now whether this poison
will work on an Upper Rank.
Big Sister...
please!
Big Sister!
This is...
stronger than the poison you used...
on Rui's mountain, isn't it?
So, they did exchange information
after all.
Poison is a double-edged sword.
You... have been changing
the concoction for each demon!
That's what he told me!
What's this?
Looks like I've neutralized your poison!
Sorry about that!
Even though you used it just for me!
That sword...
The sound it makes
when you sheathe it is unique.
Is that where you change up the poison?
Wow, this is fun!
Getting poisoned is so amusing!
It's almost addictive!
Do you think your
next blend will work?
Let's give it a try!
Very well.
Fine by me.
After all...
I'd already anticipated
that this'd happen.
Are you done mixing your new poison?
I'm ready whenever you are!
I know I told you to give it a try...
but repeating the same strike
feels monotonous.
What's this? You're slower than before.
At this rate...
Insect Breathing, Dance of the Horsefly...
Enticing Slash!
Whoops, you got a piece of me there, huh?
You must have redirected
my counterattacks.
That's amazing! I'm truly impressed!
It's the touching fruits of your labor!
You can keep piling it on!
Why don't you launch your next attack
before I neutralize the poison?
I can't help...
wanting to cheer on people who try hard!
Yes!
That's the spirit!
Ever since I was a child,
I was kindhearted and smart.
I never failed to help the pitiful,
and I made them happy.
Because that was my duty.
There are rainbows in this child's eyes.
This pale gray hair
is proof of his innocence.
This child is special.
I'm sure that he can hear
the voices of the gods.
My parents were hopelessly obtuse.
Not that they could've
founded a stupid religion
like the Eternal Paradise Faith otherwise.
I felt sorry for them...
so I always played along.
I never once heard the voices of the gods.
At first, I didn't know how
to deal with the hordes of people
worshipping me and praying to me.
Seeing these grown-ups
come crying to a child like me...
saying, "I'm suffering,
I'm in pain, what should I do?"...
made me worry
whether their heads were okay.
After nearly putting me to sleep
with their personal stories...
they would bow down to me,
asking me to guide them to Paradise.
I cried.
You poor things.
Paradise doesn't even exist.
It's just a fairy tale
concocted by deluded humans.
There are no gods nor buddhas.
These people had lived for decades,
yet they still couldn't grasp that.
When you die, you just become nothing.
You just stop feeling anything.
Your heart stops, your brain stops,
you rot and return to the earth.
That's what happens
to every living creature.
You're incapable of accepting
such a simple fact.
It must be hard to be so stupid.
I want to bring happiness
to these pitiful people.
I want to save them!
That's why I...
was born into this world.
Hmm...
That's the fifth round.
Another dud, huh?
It's not working.
It's getting less
and less effective, isn't it?
How many more times
can you mix up that poison?
Oh, are you out of breath now?
Look at all that sweat! Are you all right?
So...
this is the power of an Upper Rank!
The poison's not working on him at all!
The speed at which
he becomes resistant is insane!
Well, the air sacs in your lungs
are going through necrosis.
Painful, isn't it?
You did breathe in
my Blood Demon Art after all.
He turns his frozen blood into mist...
and uses his fans to disperse it.
The very act of breathing itself
becomes dangerous.
I'll use...
consecutive strikes to inject him
with a massive dose of poison!
Insect Breathing...
Dance of the Dragonfly...
Compound Eye Hexagon!
My goodness...
you're incredibly fast!
You might be the fastest Hashira
I've ever met!
I've been... slashed!
If only you could've beheaded me
instead of using poison.
With your speed, you might've beaten me.
Well, maybe not!
Since you're so small!
I wonder why my hands are so small.
Why didn't I ever grow taller?
If I were just a little taller...
could I have beheaded a demon
and defeated it?
Having longer arms and legs means
you have that much more muscle.
That would give me an advantage.
My big sister was petite...
but she was taller than me.
How I envy Mr. Himejima!
Who wouldn't be relieved
to see him come to their rescue?
I know what my sister was trying to say...
that day.
Hey, is this the end?
Too bad, I guess.
"Shinobu, you'll probably lose
to that demon."
That's what you started to say,
but you stopped yourself, right?
Get yourself together.
I won't allow you to shed any tears.
Big Sister...
Stand up.
I can't! I've lost so much blood!
My left lung's punctured,
and I can't even breathe!
I don't want to hear it.
Stand up...
Insect Hashira Shinobu Kocho!
If you've made up your mind
to defeat him, then defeat him!
If you've made up
your mind to win, then win!
Win, whatever it takes.
Isn't that what you promised
both me and Kanao?
Kanao...
I'm so sorry...
I didn't finish you off,
so it must really hurt, right?
I know you can do this, Shinobu.
Give it your all.
What, you're standing up?
You're really going to stand up? Huh?
Are you... really human?
I slashed your collarbone,
your lung and your ribs.
At your size, the amount of blood
you've lost should've killed you by now.
Oh no, see?
The blood is gurgling in your lungs!
The pain must be unimaginable!
I'll slice off your head right now,
so don't push yourself!
You're past saving now.
Go ahead and let go.
I should go for his
Achilles' heel... his neck!
If I slam the poison into his neck,
I'll have a chance!
Insect Breathing...
Dance of the Centipede...
Hmm?
Hundred-legged Zigzag!
She's twisting
and turning in all directions.
The impact of her steps
is enough to destroy the bridge.
So fast! I can't predict her attack!
So low!
The road to bliss.
I always believed...
that it continued to stretch on and on...
far into the distance.
Not until it was destroyed...
did I realize that my bliss
sat on top of a sliver of glass.
And...
just as we'd been rescued...
I wanted to become stronger...
and protect...
someone else's unscathed happiness.
That's what we'd...
promised each other.
"Let's defeat the demons."
"As many as we can."
"Together."
So that others wouldn't have to...
go through what we did!
Even if I'm weak.
Even if I was incapable
of beheading a demon!
By defeating a single demon...
I could save dozens!
And if the demon I brought down
was an Upper Rank...
I could save hundreds of people!
It's not a matter of whether
I can do it or not.
It's something that I have to do.
Are you angry?
Yes, I am angry, Tanjiro.
I'm always...
constantly...
angry.
My parents were killed.
My big sister was killed.
My Tsuguko
other than Kanao were all killed.
Not to mention those girls.
If their loved ones...
hadn't been murdered by demons...
they'd still be living happily
with their families!
You make me so livid!
Don't you mess with me, idiot!
Why isn't the poison
working on you, dammit?
You bastard!
So commendable!
You did your best!
My heart is moved!
To see such a weak girl
getting this far...
How did you last this long
as a Demon Slayer...
with less talent than your big sister?
It's a miracle
that you survived until now!
So foolish, you'll try
to see things through
to the end despite the futility!
That's what makes humans so fragile!
And it's what makes humans so magnificent!
You're worthy of being devoured by me!
Let's share eternity, you and I!
Any last words?
I'll be happy to listen.
Go to hell!
Master!
I bet he's here, too.
Since I'm sure...
he also needs to face me!
The people you love and hold dear...
We just thoughtlessly assume
that they'll still be alive tomorrow
and the day after.
But...
that's nothing but a desire.
Flower Breathing...
And even though...
it's not an ironclad promise...
Fourth Form...
Crimson Hanagoromo!
Whoa, that was close!
...they'll always be alive and close by.
For some reason...
people can't help believing that.
Would you mind not attacking me
while I'm absorbing her?
What's this?
You're not taking the bait?
Is it because of what she motioned earlier
with her fingers?
Did she tell you what my powers are?
In just a split second? Amazing!
Even though it's futile.
She's such a hard worker!
But really, I have to say...
what a wonderful night this is.
The feasts just keep coming...
one after another.
Yes, truly...
what a wonderful night.
You're here, aren't you?
Show yourself.
I know you're there.
That's no way to talk, you know.
Not to your senior.
You look a little better than before...
but you're still the same
scrawny guy as ever.
UPPER SIX
Long time no see...
Zenitsu.
Kaigaku...
Now that you're a demon...
I no longer consider you my senior!
Water Breathing...
Ninth Form...
Splashing Water Flow, Turbulent!
Stay focused!
Right!
This place is crazy!
The buildings themselves are throbbing
like they're pulsing!
It's like it's alive!
It's trying to tear Mr. Giyu and me apart!
We have to reconvene with as many
other Corps members as we can...
and head to where Muzan is!
Deceased!
Shinobu Kocho has died!
After battling Upper Two...
she's now deceased!
That crow...
What's that piece of paper on its neck?
The communications are up so quickly.
Shinobu is dead.
You mustn't look downward.
Just think about
what you're going to do next.
- Right!
What's the status of the other Hashira
and Corps members?
At the center of the 40th vertical
and 12th horizontal levels...
the Corps members are fighting demons.
Numbering at least ten.
And beyond that wall,
more than 30 demons are now approaching.
Mr. Yushiro's eyes
can see Blood Demon Arts.
The art itself that is not visible
to human eyes.
These lights of different sizes
must be the potency
of each demon's Blood Demon Art.
And these pulsating buildings
in constant motion...
are also a Blood Demon Art.
And there seems to be no end to it.
Such incredible power.
This is...
a demon castle, spreading out infinitely!
And we have been lured
inside this infinite demon castle.
But...
it's not as if we were just drawn in.
My father prepared
for this day meticulously...
and here we are now.
Using Gyomei as the linchpin...
he had the Hashira positioned
to arrive on the scene at any time...
and in order to align
all of the individual Corps members...
he gave the Kasugai Crows
their missions and waited.
Enlisting the aid
of both Ms. Tamayo and Mr. Yushiro...
and finally...
to ensure that this plan
would be perfect...
my sisters also sacrificed their lives...
along with those of our parents.
We will not...
lose this battle!
Five massive powers are being emitted
throughout this great space...
as if flaunting their own strength.
These must be the Upper Ranks.
One of them is at the same spot
where Shinobu was located.
Upper Rank sighting!
Upper Six and Agatsuma
have encountered each other!
An Upper Rank! Are there
any other Corps members with him?
None! Agatsuma is alone!
The odds aren't good for a lone Hinoe!
Send him backup right away!
You haven't changed, have you?
You're still a runt and shabby-looking...
and weak as ever.
Were you able to become a Hashira?
Hey, Zenitsu!
Did you ever learn to use
anything besides the First Form?
Someone seems thrilled to have made it
as an Upper Rank
bottom-feeder as a stopgap.
Hah!
You sure learned to mouth off.
Why did you become a demon of all things?
You would never--
Why would the prospective heir
of Thunder Breathing become a demon?
Huh?
Because you turned into a demon...
Gramps...
committed seppuku and died!
committed seppuku alone!
Without any assistance!
If you don't have
someone cut off your head
after you've stabbed
yourself in the belly...
you die a drawn-out death in agony!
Gramps...
died without even stabbing
his own throat or heart!
All because a demon was produced
from a Thunder Breathing user!
What do I care?
So? What is it?
You want me to grieve?
To repent and atone for my ways?
I have no use for anyone
who doesn't value me.
I always...
no matter what...
take the side of whoever knows my worth.
If the old geezer died in agony, I'm glad.
After all that I did for him...
instead of making me his successor...
he had the gall to make trash like you
my co-successor, that bastard!
Former Hashira or not...
I have no use for a senile geezer!
Gramps wasn't senile by a long shot.
If I'm trash, then you're scum!
Between me, who could
only use the First Form,
and you, who could
never use the First Form...
I feel sorry for Gramps to have
such a sorry pair of successors!
Don't lump me together...
with the likes of you!
Thunder Breathing...
Fourth Form...
Distant Thunder!
You're too slow, scum.
He slashed me!
So fast!
He's...
moving like a totally different person!
I'm not wrong!
There's no shame in kneeling down
before the overwhelmingly powerful.
As long as you're alive,
you'll find a way.
You haven't lost until the moment you die.
Whether you grovel on the ground...
whether you have no home...
and have to drink from a puddle...
whether they condemn you
for stealing money...
as long as you're alive,
you can win some day.
I'll win and prove it.
Believing that has kept me going in life.
Do you wish to gain even more power...
by becoming a demon?
Should that man acknowledge you...
then you, too, will become one of us.
The stronger the swordsman...
the longer it takes for him
to become a demon.
It took me three full days.
Turning a wielder
of a Breathing Technique into a demon...
will require a massive amount
of that man's blood.
And though rare...
some are physically
incapable of becoming demons...
I wonder how you will fare.
You must appreciate this blood.
Do not even think
of spilling a single drop.
Should you let any fall...
your head and torso...
will be severed.
That terror that felt
like every cell in my body...
was screaming and sobbing...
Compared to that...
this little punk is nothing!
Just 'cause he's stronger doesn't mean
he's on par with an Upper Rank!
Zenitsu Agatsuma... This guy is trash!
He was always sniveling like a baby!
Not a shred of dignity or grit!
Help me!
There's a pitfall!
I twisted my ankle!
Me, co-successor with this trash?
That damn geezer was full of it!
Here you go, Kaigaku.
Gramps!
It's a little too big, see?
- Come on, Gramps!
- You and me, equals?
There's just no way in hell!
He deserved to die!
That goes for both you
and that old geezer!
You both deserve to die!
I could only learn the First Form...
and you were able to learn
everything but the First Form.
That's why Gramps...
wanted us both to be
his Thunder Breathing successors.
But you wanted so badly
to deny him that...
you became a demon, didn't you?
Here it comes!
Thunder Breathing...
Second Form...
Rice Spirit!
With one breath, five flashes
in the blink of an eye!
You must've devoured tons of people!
You can't even tell right from wrong
any more, can you?
Oh, I know the difference
between right and wrong!
What's the matter?
Aren't you the old geezer's favorite?
So, why don't you show me...
what he graciously passed down to you?
What's wrong?
Don't hold back!
Just hit me with it already!
Thunder Breathing...
First Form...
Thunderclap and Flash!
Such a basic move where all you do
is charge at me head-on...
so brainlessly...
could never hit me!
Thunder Breathing...
Third Form...
Thunder Swarm!
He's attacking me in waves while spinning!
What's wrong?
Are you done already?
Thunder Breathing...
First Form...
Thunderclap and Flash! Eightfold!
It's not working!
Thunder Breathing...
Fifth Form...
Heat Lightning!
How does it feel?
The bite of my
Blood Demon Art-enhanced sword?
A deadly strike that cracks...
and burns your skin and flesh!
Those who correctly evaluate
and recognize my value are good!
Those who write me off
and fail to acknowledge me are evil!
Do you get it now?
This is my power now!
The power I gained
by becoming a demon, that is!
Single thunderclap or eightfold or what...
making you his successor
when that's all you can do...
was a total misjudgment!
So, that's the answer
you've come up with, huh?
I knew it.
I always knew it, but still...
Zenitsu!
This...
is the end!
Thunder Breathing...
Sixth Form...
Rumble and Flash!
That strike will keep cracking
throughout your body!
Burn it into your mind and body!
My power!
Now that I'm a demon,
I've surpassed Thunder Breathing!
I'm special!
I'm not like you!
I'm not like any of you!
It looks like the old geezer
struck out with you after all!
Be more like Kaigaku!
Try to be like your senior!
Isn't the First Form the entire basis
of Thunder Breathing?
If the First Form's the only one
he can't use, doesn't that mean... Y'know?
He may have mastered other forms,
but he's no big deal.
But even still,
that Kaigaku guy's so arrogant.
No way can he become a Hashira.
He'll probably croak right away anyway.
Wh-What do you think you're doing?
I hear you punched
a higher-ranking Corps member.
Don't go around making trouble, you trash!
How shameful that someone like you exists!
I was fully aware that Kaigaku hated me...
and I hated him right back.
But I respected you.
I truly did.
You were such a hard worker,
and you kept grinding away.
I always looked up to you as an example.
You were special, you know.
For both Gramps and me,
you were special and important!
But...
I guess that wasn't enough for you.
No matter what...
I always heard a sound
of discontent from you.
There's a hole in the box
where you store the joy in your heart.
And the joy just keeps leaking out.
You have to spot the hole
and close it up...
or the box will never be filled.
Gramps...
I'm sorry.
We ended up...
taking different paths!
He still has some strength left?
Wh-What the hell?
Sorry...
Big Brother.
Thunder Breathing...
Seventh Form...
God of Fire Thunder!
I...
I couldn't see that coming!
What the hell is that move?
It's too fast!
I've never seen that technique!
What the hell did you just use?
Dammit! Dammit!
I knew that old fart always favored you!
He only taught you that technique
and never showed me!
You're wrong!
Gramps wasn't that kind of man!
It's my own technique.
My own exclusive technique
that I came up with myself.
I was hoping to one day...
use this technique...
to battle by your side.
A seventh technique?
Thunder Breathing only has six techniques,
and he created a seventh?
Him?
A guy who can only use the First Form?
That trash who's inferior to me?
I can't take it! I just can't take it!
No way can I accept that as a fact!
A guy like that... Me, lose to him?
I think I'm losing my mind!
No...
Wait, it's not a loss!
That trash is going to fall
with me and die, too!
His strength's depleted by now for sure!
He's going to die along with me!
Those who don't give to others
end up never receiving from others.
Guys who do nothing but want
are the same as those who possess nothing.
Because they can't
produce anything themselves.
Dying alone is pathetic, huh?
Where am I?
Gramps!
Sorry! I couldn't get along with Kaigaku!
I did write him letters and stuff!
But he never replied!
If it weren't for me,
Kaigaku might not have ended up like that!
I'm really sorry! Forgive me!
Sorry that I couldn't pay you back
for all that you did for me!
I wanted to become a Hashira
while you were alive, but...
Sorry!
Sorry, Gramps!
Do you hate me now?
Please! Say something, Gramps!
Dammit!
What's this grabbing onto my legs?
Gramps! I... I...
Dammit!
Zenitsu...
You're my pride and joy.
Well?
Can you save him?
He's my acquaintance!
Find a way to save him!
I'm really counting on you!
Quiet down. Shut up, Murata.
A lowly scrub like you...
Better keep watch
so we don't get attacked.
Hey you! What rank are you?
If you're below me,
there'll be hell to pay!
I'm a demon,
so what do I care about ranks?
I'm using a Blood Demon styptic...
but if these cracks on
his face keep spreading,
it's going to rip all the
way to his eyeballs.
Can you hear me?
Don't say scary things
to someone so vulnerable!
I'm also using a hemostatic,
but the bleeding won't stop.
Stop it!
I swear you'll be fine!
You'll be saved for sure!
You're not gonna die!
You can do it, Agatsuma!
Hang in there! Hang in there!
The Upper Rank that you fought
still hadn't mastered
his techniques and abilities.
That was a lucky break for you.
If you'd fought him a year from now,
you probably would've died instantly.
Stop saying stuff...
that will crush his soul!
I-I didn't say anything wrong!
Wh-What?
You yelled, so now the demons are coming.
You make a good target.
Hey, was your name Yushiro?
I'm leaving Agatsuma in your hands!
Come on!
Please defeat it
as fast as you can, Senpai.
I'm going to give you
such an earful later!
Dammit!
Water Breathing, Second Form...
Water Wheel!
We're going to head them off,
so go from that direction!
Not good! They're going to run into one!
We're not running into any Upper Ranks.
Are we still far off from where Muzan is?
Are the others still alive?
Ms. Shinobu...
We're going to win for sure!
Everyone will!
We all will!
What's this shaking?
M-Mr. Giyu!
Stop!
Calm down.
Is someone else fighting?
Is someone else about to die?
No, that's not it.
Is it coming this way?
Th-This scent...
Above you! Tanjiro, fall back!
Long time no see.
I'm surprised you're still alive.
A weakling like you...
UPPER THREE
Tanjiro...
Kamado!
Akaza!
Most likely...
he's decomposing the drug
to turn him back
into a human inside this flesh cocoon.
Muzan Kibutsuji...
No matter what...
you absolutely must be destroyed!
And yet...
no matter what I do...
Eventually...
I'll be absorbed into him, as well!
Please...
somebody...
come soon!
Please!
According to Father, should Muzan die,
the other demons will also die.
In that case,
Muzan Kibutsuji is still alive.
Ms. Tamayo must be suppressing
Muzan's powers.
It's because she's suppressing them
that he hasn't reacted
to Mr. Yushiro's eyes.
Before Muzan's powers are revived...
we must do whatever it takes
to defeat him.
Still...
inside this...
infinite castle...
can we really find Muzan Kibutsuji?
No need to panic.
You're doing a good job.
He will show himself without fail.
Didn't he come to me, as well?
That's the kind of man...
Muzan Kibutsuji is.
Understood...
Father.
I will fulfill my duty, no matter what!
We must find him before the Corps members'
strength is depleted...
and settle this once and for all!
Shield them!
We're going to stand our ground
and minimize the damage to the Hashira!
Ahead! Please go on ahead!
Stone Hashira, please hurry!
You guys...
Whatever you do, please defeat Kibutsuji!
Please!
All right.
I'm counting on you all to deal with this!
Tokito!
Now's the time to prove
what we gained from Hashira Training!
Right!
Thanks, all of you.
Father, everyone's giving it their all.
No crying.
Don't stop what you're doing,
no matter what.
We're not going down in defeat.
Right.
Lord Kiriya is so commendable.
He's still in anguish
over the loss of his father...
yet he's assumed command
of the Demon Slayer Corps...
and is working to fulfill his duty.
Am I right, Mr. Rengoku?
I agree.
Look how these children of such
a tender age are rallying themselves.
Like Kyojuro...
in order to live up to the Rengoku name...
I will protect them with my life.
She looks as if she's suffering.
The demon named Tamayo, who was working
with the Master, sent over this drug.
I've administered it as she instructed...
but can Nezuko
actually turn back into a human?
If Nezuko does become human again,
Muzan's scheme will collapse.
The dream of the perfect body,
for which he's searched
for more than a thousand years...
his quest to conquer the sun
will be set back to square one.
Throughout all these long years,
Nezuko is the only demon
not to succumb to sunlight.
The words "the final stage"
keep crossing my mind.
And each time, I tremble at my core,
and my heart pounds.
This long battle may finally end tonight.
I never dreamed
that I'd be alive to see it myself.
Tanjiro...
Now that I think of it,
ever since that moment when you
brought your demon sister to me...
a great cogwheel of some kind
seems to have started turning.
If the by-product of all our battles
until now can be likened
to a giant machine...
then inserting you and Nezuko
into it as two small cogs...
is what set the stagnant situation
into motion.
Don't lose, Nezuko!
Don't lose, Tanjiro!
Whatever you do, don't lose!
Hinokami Kagura...
Fire Wheel!
Go! Go! Go! If I can't even sever his arm,
I'll never sever his head!
I severed it!
I was able to dodge his attack, too!
I can do it! I can fight him!
I couldn't go for his head!
But next time...
Hinokami Kagura...
Fake Rainbow!
Tanjiro...
You've really honed your techniques.
It wouldn't be exaggerating to say
that your skills are at Hashira level.
You can hold your own like this
against Upper Three!
That day...
you'd lost all hope in the snow...
unable to do anything
but bow your head...
and sob as you begged
for your sister's life.
But now you can fight.
To keep from being robbed
of your life and dignity.
"This boy isn't weak! Don't insult him."
I admit that Kyojuro
was right in saying that.
You indeed were not weak.
Hats off to you!
Technique Development...
Well, let's get this party started.
It's time to have some fun.
Water Breathing...
Third Form...
Flowing Dance!
The Water Hashira, huh?
Great...
It's been 50 years
since I last ran into one!
Destructive Death...
Disorder!
Water Breathing, Eleventh Form...
Dead Calm!
I've never seen that move before.
The Water Hashira I killed before
didn't use it!
Hinokami Kagura...
Raging Sun!
He... vanished?
Behind me?
Hinokami Kagura, Fake Rain--
Water Breathing, Second Form...
Water Wheel!
Hinokami Kagura...
Flame Dance!
Destructive Death, Leg Type...
Crown Splitter!
I caught it with my sword!
Did it graze me?
Just a bit?
And it's this powerful?
That's elegant!
What a polished sword skill that is!
Magnificent!
Tell me your name!
What is your name?
I want to remember you!
I don't have a name to divulge to a demon!
I hate talking, so don't speak to me!
I see, so you're not into talking?
I happen to love talking!
I'm going to keep asking you, then...
what your name is!
Destructive Death...
Leg Type...
Explosive Flurry!
Mr. Giyu!
I see!
So, his name is Giyu!
Hinokami Kagura...
Destructive Death...
Eight-Layered Demon Core!
Burning Bones, Summer Sun!
Good moves.
You did well to train to this level
in such a short time.
You have my praise.
Still, Kyojuro did a damn fine job.
Crumpled on the ground that night,
you were an absolute weakling.
You were nothing but a weed.
But what do you know?
Look at you now!
Such eye-opening growth!
I'm purely elated!
This makes my heart race!
I'm glad that Kyojuro died that night.
Otherwise, he might never have gotten
any stronger than he was.
After all, he did have those lame values,
wanting to remain a human.
What did you say?
You...
don't say another word.
Don't you dare talk about Mr. Rengoku!
Why not?
These are words of praise.
For you, as well. For Kyojuro, too.
No, they're not!
All you're doing is insulting him!
You're just spitting on him, that's all!
On everyone!
You're mistaken, Tanjiro.
You see...
the only thing I hate is a weakling.
I would only spit on a weakling,
no one else.
That's right.
The weak make my skin crawl.
They make me vomit.
They're weeded out
due to the law of nature, nothing else.
Everything you just said is wrong!
Your being here now is proof of that!
Everyone's a weak infant at birth!
We can't stay alive
without someone else's help!
That goes for you, too, Akaza.
You may not remember it,
but when you were a baby,
you were protected
and helped by someone...
and that's why you're alive now!
The strong save and protect the weak!
And the weak become strong and save
and protect those weaker than themselves!
That's the law of nature!
Akaza, I won't tolerate
your way of thinking!
I won't let you have your way anymore!
I get it now.
I have a deep-seated aversion to this guy.
He's stronger, but my revulsion
for him hasn't faded!
Whatever they do...
everyone starts out as a baby.
We learn by getting help
from those around us.
We are not competing against each other.
The opponent you're up against
will always be you yourself.
The important thing is to become
stronger than you were yesterday.
If you can keep that up
for a decade or two,
that would be commendable.
And then...
it'll be you helping out others this time.
What was that? He just swung at nothing.
Tanjiro...
You repulse me after all.
Destructive Death, Crushing Type...
Ten Thousand Leaves Flashing Willow!
So fast! Insanely fast!
No...
it's not really about speed!
This sensation, this precision...
this is...
Destructive Death, Leg Type...
From below!
Flying Planet Thousand Wheels!
Even if I manage to predict
his movements and intercept the attack,
the impact is so strong,
I can't escape unscathed!
A technique of unparalleled precision!
He can pierce through any opening
with the accuracy of a compass!
It's like there are magnets
pulling his blows
straight to the human body's vitals!
But how?
What is this?
What's causing them
to be drawn in like this?
Try to remember! Think!
There's got to be something!
If you can find a clue
in what Akaza has said
and done until now...
Hinokami Kagura...
Solar Heat Haze!
Interesting technique!
I know I dodged it for sure,
but then it looked like
the blade extended.
I don't know what kind
of swing you put on it...
but the tip of your blade wavered
like it was in a heat haze! I'm intrigued!
Hinokami Kagura...
Dance!
Oh, crap!
He's going to break it!
That's a good head-butt!
Let go! Let go! Let go!
No good! He's not letting go!
Mr. Giyu!
I'm furious right now.
Because my back is absolutely killing me.
How dare you hurl me all that distance...
Upper Three?
Personally...
I'd rather not draw my sword
if I can help it...
and I don't enjoy sparring
random passersby for amusement.
But right now...
I can feel that facing a strong opponent
who overwhelms me for
the first time in a while...
has sharply honed my senses
in a short span of time.
My dormant senses
have been rudely awakened
and are dragging me forward.
To the place where the strong one stands.
I understand now
how much it expands one's potential...
to fight to the death...
until the very last moment.
Mr. Giyu...
A mark appeared. His speed...
Has increased!
Water Breathing, Fourth Form...
Striking Tide!
So fast! Both of them!
But in response
to Mr. Giyu's speed boost...
Akaza adapted instantly!
Is that the best you can do?
More!
Strike more attacks on me!
Tenth Form...
Constant Flux!
Seventh Form...
Drop Ripple Thrust!
Destructive Death...
Disorder!
Mr. Giyu!
Akaza!
Calm down!
Think. Don't panic.
Don't relinquish your mind
whatever you do!
Why are Akaza's attacks
as accurate as magnets?
Why does he unfailingly react to attacks
from behind and in his blind spots?
Think!
Your fighting spirit
has been honed to the hilt.
It's close to the realm of the highest.
Akaza used the words "fighting spirit"...
during his battle with Mr. Rengoku.
What's "fighting spirit"?
As I can sense all kinds of things
through scent...
Akaza seems to sense things
through fighting spirit.
It tingles, you know.
Where the enemy is aiming at.
So, that's how you knew
that Gyutaro was attacking you.
Even though it was from behind!
That was awesome!
Well, my skin is tougher
than most people's!
Whether it's from behind or not,
if someone is looking at me,
I can tell that they're looking!
Can you show me?
Sure thing!
You're looking
at my right shoulder, aren't you?
Wow! You got it!
I can tell right away
especially if someone is looking at me
with killing intent!
Since anyone who could harm me
is bad news.
Killing intent feels like it's stabbing me
through the skin.
That's right,
Inosuke could sense the invisible
through his honed sense of touch.
What else did we talk about...
that day?
But the thing is,
it's hard to catch onto someone
without any killing intent or hostility.
- That tiny hag!
- Huh?
The old hag from the house
with the wisteria family
crest was a real terror.
Before I knew it...
she'd be sitting behind me
holding rice balls!
You shouldn't call her a "hag"!
She's an elderly lady!
- Elderly hag!
- Hey!
That got me thinking.
If I can sneak up without letting out
any killing intent, I won't be detected!
Then there wouldn't be anyone
I couldn't kill!
Hmm,
but isn't that because she didn't have
any intention of harming you?
I think that killing a demon
without emitting any killing intent
would be impossible.
Well, you're probably right.
A half-hearted strike
without any killing intent
couldn't cut through...
a demon's hard neck.
It was just a casual conversation,
but I think he was on to something bigger.
What is it that Akaza supposedly senses
as fighting spirit?
Is it not killing intent?
Is it the will to fight?
The amount of time spent training?
Or maybe the quantity?
Is it like the way I can anticipate
movements through scent?
Isn't there any way
that I can disrupt Akaza's compass?
Hinokami Kagura...
Dance!
Your torso is wide open...
Tanjiro!
It's coming!
Fighting spirit, magnet...
compass...
perception, killing intent...
the impossible...
the realm of the highest...
I see.
That's what it is.
Father...
When you perform
the Hinokami Kagura dance,
what are you thinking?
If it's too tiring for you, Father,
I'll take your place starting next year.
I'm worried about your health.
Thank you, Tanjiro.
But I haven't found the Kagura
to be tiring for the last few years.
I don't know how to explain it,
but back when I first learned
it from your grandfather...
even though I was younger, healthier
and stronger than I am now,
I kept losing my breath,
and it was so hard.
The Kagura performed
at the start of each year
was passed down through
the Kamado Family lineage.
It was a grueling event
that went on interminably
from sunset to dawn the next morning.
There are 12 different styles,
which are repeated until daybreak...
hundreds, thousands,
tens of thousands of times.
I think I was simply making
too many wasteful motions.
The important thing
is to breathe correctly
and to move correctly.
To produce maximum strength
with minimal action.
By doing that, your mind
gradually becomes transparent.
Transparent?
At first, you need to memorize
all of the movements
and acquire a feel for it.
You open up all five senses
and become aware of the shape
of your own body vessel by vessel.
That was the truly strenuous part.
All you can think is that,
even if you go on struggling,
you'll never succeed.
After you've learned all these things
and absorbed them,
you remove what you don't need.
Only leave what you need
for that movement...
and close the rest.
Close the rest?
You know people often close their eyes
when they're trying to hear better?
Just like that, you pick out the things
you need the most in that moment.
Eventually, you'll be able
to open and close
the vessels and muscles in your body...
as quickly and easily
as if you were blinking.
When that happens, a path
illuminated by a bright light will open.
When your mind becomes transparent,
you can start to see
the Transparent World.
But this is a domain...
you can only reach after
you've struggled and suffered,
pushing yourself to your limits.
Do you think I can get there, too?
If you keep working at it tirelessly, yes.
Here, all done.
Thanks!
Ten days before my father passed away...
a bear attacked and devoured people
on a neighboring mountain.
We lit bonfires around the house
and put up ropes with bells on them.
Tanjiro...
Yes?
Come with me.
I'm sorry that you're hungry,
but I won't let you come any closer.
If anyone tries to harm my family,
I will show no mercy no matter
how many of them there are.
Disregard my warning...
and I will take your life.
The bear's head,
as thick as a human torso,
dropped to the ground
with the sound of the bells.
My eyes couldn't follow it,
but I think my father slashed it
twice in the blink of an eye.
Otherwise,
it wouldn't have been possible to chop
off its head with an axe of that breadth.
My father's scent
never wavered in the least.
Before and after beheading the bear,
he emitted no fear,
no uncertainty, no killing intent.
Did you get a good look?
Don't forget what you just saw.
My father wasn't one
to flaunt his strength for no reason.
I realized this later on.
That was...
him letting me watch and learn.
So that I could learn from observing
the body movements of my father...
who could see the Transparent World.
Just like Father, Grandfather
and Great-Grandfather...
must've all done before me.
You must never give up.
Just keep thinking.
You can break through
any wall eventually...
with tireless effort.
I know, Father.
That's why...
I was able to dodge
Akaza's magnetic, inescapable blow!
That was probably a lethal blow
meant to kill me once and for all.
When I was alternating moves
with Mr. Giyu...
I could take momentary breaks...
and he protected me
from the potentially mortal blows!
But in that instant,
even Mr. Giyu couldn't make it in time!
However, for some reason...
in that moment, it didn't feel impossible.
I felt it for just a split second.
I was able to enter it
for just a split second.
That world.
The Transparent World.
His body looked transparent.
The same as when Hantengu
was hiding inside his own heart.
I don't know if I was able
to see him or if I smelled him.
Dodge.
I focused on just that,
and I closed off all other senses.
My body moved faster
than it ever had before.
When I'm able to enter
the Transparent World
that Father told me about,
my ability to predict movements,
and the speed of my
attacks improve dramatically!
I can see my opponent's lungs moving...
his vessels flowing and contracting
through his body.
I can even see my own muscles contracting.
Faster...
and even clearer!
I may be able to close off
the fighting spirit
that Akaza is likely detecting...
and aim for his head!
See it.
See it!
It looks like you've thrown
every last Water Form you have at me.
That's enough, Giyu.
Let's end this!
I'm impressed that you held out this long!
No way!
In the middle of the downswing...
he snapped it...
from the side!
Farewell.
He slashed his arm amidst his strike
and stopped him.
The sound of his breathing is different.
His hair and eyes, too!
I've been saved by Tanjiro.
Every cell in my body,
right down to the tips of my hairs,
is telling me to kill him this instant.
He's undergone some kind of change.
He's dangerous.
He's focusing on Tanjiro.
Now's my chance!
Technique Development Final Form...
Blue Silver Chaotic Afterglow!
He's boosting his attack speed again!
The force is increasing!
Can I take it...
with Dead Calm?
This is what Father was talking about.
This is...
the Transparent World!
What's this?
It's so strange.
Time is passing by so slowly.
No...
is it just that the movements look slow?
Unavoidable.
He made 100 blows almost simultaneously.
I couldn't block them all
even with Dead Calm.
That was impressive.
As expected, you survived.
It looks like you managed
to evade any fatal blows.
No need for you to die
like Kyojuro and Tanjiro.
You should become a demon, too, Giyu!
He hasn't noticed!
That Tanjiro's behind him!
Does he have no presence?
This is...
Tanjiro, slash him!
If you can still move, go for it!
Before he notices you!
Take his head!
Akaza! I'm going to behead you now!
He gave himself away?
He's alive?
I never dreamed
that after that attack, he'd still...
No, it's not a big deal!
My Destructive Death, Compass Needle
can detect any attack!
The stronger
my opponent's fighting spirit is,
the greater my Compass Needle's reaction!
What is that?
What's that bizarre presence?
It's like he's turned into
some other creature!
This guy...
His fighting spirit's gone!
He has no fighting spirit!
Calm down!
He's coming!
Hinokami Kagura...
Setting Sun Transformation.
Im... possible!
In the last several hundred years,
I've never once seen a human
without any fighting spirit!
Even newborns have traces of it!
And yet, in that instant,
his fighting spirit completely vanished!
It was like I was facing
an anomaly that shouldn't be there...
and my senses were thrown into confusion.
My Compass Needle detected nothing.
But that's not the issue here!
On the battlefield,
you must instantly understand
the unforeseen and the unexpected...
and deal with them then and there!
I have the ability to do that!
Or so I thought.
But during this short battle,
he grasped something
and surpassed my speed!
The very best of martial arts,
honed over several centuries...
He shattered them with a head-on attack!
There was no hatred or rage in his eyes...
no killing intent
or fighting spirit, either!
Most likely, those eyes
had perceived what I've been seeking...
the realm of the highest!
None other than the selfless state.
I've had a vague sense
that this state existed...
but I've never yet managed to attain it.
I'm not done yet!
I can still fight!
I can still become stronger!
Is he trying to... reattach his head?
I can't let it end!
Not here!
I'm going to get stronger!
I've got to become stronger
than anyone else!
Stronger!
Even stronger.
It disintegrated!
It's over now!
We won!
I'm so dizzy...
My muscles are cramping.
My body's reached its limit!
Are you all right? Tanjiro--
His body isn't disintegrating!
Does this...
- Does this mean...
- Tan--
He's still moving!
His body's not crumbling!
The severed part is closing up!
So dizzy...
No way... No way!
Even after I cut off his head,
he still won't die?
Is there some kind of condition to meet?
Like with Gyutaro and Daki?
No, that's not it.
His head crumbled and disappeared!
He's trying to change right now!
Akaza's also...
trying to evolve into something else!
He's trying to become like Muzan,
whose head is not his weak point!
This battle isn't over!
The fight is still--
Tanjiro!
He fainted!
Well, of course!
He's long since blown past his limit!
Water Breathing...
Fourth Form...
Striking Tide!
He's regenerating!
Even after losing his head,
his speed is...
I can't hear a thing out of my left ear.
I have no sensation in my right hand.
I can still grip with it,
but I don't know how useful I'll be.
Hold it!
I...
I'm...
still alive!
If you want to kill Tanjiro,
you'll have to defeat me first!
An indomitable spirit...
It will never bend
no matter what crisis it finds itself in.
We're not samurai.
We don't carry swords.
But we always carry swords in our hearts.
All we use...
are our own fists.
You are...
an eyesore!
Please stop.
Who is that?
Mr. Hakuji...
Please stop already!
Let go.
Let go of my hand!
Who the hell are you?
Let's stop this right now!
Let's go to the other side!
I can't.
I've got to kill those two!
Why is that?
I've got to become stronger!
I'll kill anyone who gets in my way!
Why is that?
Why do you wish to become stronger?
Because...
unless I'm strong...
I can't bring it back home
for him anymore!
The medicine for my dad!
I've got to become stronger...
or I won't be able to run off
with the wallet I stole!
I've got to become stronger...
or I won't be able to defeat them
when they retaliate!
I've got to become stronger...
or I'll get caught by the magistrate
and lashed as punishment!
You've already got three tattoos
for pickpocketing on both arms!
Next time,
we're going to chop off your hands!
Lower your head! Kneel more!
Go ahead and chop them off!
Even if you chop both hands off,
I'll still have my feet!
I'll use my feet to steal!
Regardless,
I'm not gonna get caught next time!
A repeat offender
at the tender age of 11...
And all this bravado
after taking 100 lashes
that would make grown men faint!
You're a demon child!
Call me whatever you want!
That's right, I'm a demon child!
They say I already had teeth
when I was born after all!
Insolent boy!
You little punk!
"Demon child" is fine by me, you bastards!
SOUTH TOWN MAGISTRATE'S OFFICE
Hakuji!
Your father heard that you'd been caught
stealing again, and he hanged himself!
He's dead!
Dear Hakuji...
Live an honest life.
You can still start over.
So, the poor...
aren't even allowed to live?
Dad...
To hell with this rotten world!
Every last one of you...
You can all just die and rot in hell!
Why do scumbags like these get to live...
when my dad had to go and die?
You weren't causing any trouble!
Why would you apologize?
You didn't do anything wrong, Dad!
I didn't even mind
getting lashed for stealing!
Even if they beat me black-and-blue
or broke my bones...
I could take it all for you, Dad!
For centuries, even!
Repent!
Earn an honest living!
Why don't you shut up, scum?
I don't have enough money.
Medicine costs a lot!
My dad was getting thinner and thinner.
The bones were starting
to jut out of his back.
I want him to have something
more nutritious to eat!
I would've been happy to die...
if it were for my dad's sake!
For my...
dad's sake!
Oh, wow! That is impressive!
I was called here because someone said
a child was about to be killed,
but you've flattened seven grown-ups
with your bare fists.
You've got talent, kid!
To take on grown-ups unarmed
and still win!
That's what I like to see!
Who the hell is that?
What am I seeing?
Are these my memories?
Wanna join my dojo?
I don't have any students.
Shut up, you stupid old geezer!
I'll kill you!
Those tattoos tell me...
that you're a criminal from Edo, right?
So, you've been banished from Edo,
and you ended up here?
So, what if I did?
That's none of your business!
Yes! First off,
time to be reborn, young man.
All right, bring it!
You...
drop dead, you old fart!
SORYU DOJO
Well, you sure are durable.
After that pummeling I gave you,
you came to in less than an hour.
I'm Keizo.
I run a dojo where I teach
the Soryu Style of
fighting with bare hands.
But I don't have a single student...
so I earn a living
as a handyman, doing odd jobs.
The first thing I want you to do
is look after my sickly daughter.
Since I have work,
I'd like to leave her in your care.
My wife drowned herself the other day
due to nursing fatigue.
I'm really at my wits' end
as you can see.
Really, thanks to my incompetence...
both my wife and daughter have suffered.
Are you sure you want
to leave a criminal like me
alone with your daughter?
I pummeled
the criminal out of you earlier...
so it's fine.
They're alike.
I get it now.
The reason you repulsed me...
was because you reminded me
of my worthless past.
This is my daughter, Koyuki.
My worthless past...
Worthless...
Hakuji...
I'm so sorry.
How are you, Koyuki?
Is it okay for you to be up?
Yes.
You're right, you have more color
than you did this morning.
Do you feel a bit better?
Yes.
Oh, him?
His name is...
I've asked him numerous times,
but he won't tell me.
Hey, don't just stand out there!
Have a seat here.
All right, get it out of him
before I get home!
Um...
Y-Your face...
You're hurt.
Are you all right?
I'll heal you for sure.
I'll save you...
protect you...
All I ever did in my worthless life...
was spew baseless lies.
Thank you.
You don't have to thank me
every single time.
Don't worry about it. Go to sleep.
I'm sorry...
for causing you trouble.
I said it was all right.
Do you want me to shut this?
No...
you can leave it as is.
Koyuki was truly delicate and frail.
I had to stay with her all night...
change the towels
for her forehead and her nightgown...
and give her water frequently.
When she needed to use the restroom,
it was a given I had to carry her there.
I'd already been taking care of my dad,
and since I had extraordinary
physical endurance,
it really wasn't a hardship for me.
Sorry to make you do this every day.
Why do people suffering from illness
always say they're sorry?
"Sorry to put you through all this."
"Sorry the sound
of my coughing bothers you."
"Sorry I can't work like I should."
They'd rather care
for themselves if they could.
And it's not like they can
just stop coughing.
If they could breathe normally,
they would.
They're the ones
who must be suffering the most.
Sorry again.
You can't even train because of me...
and you can't go play.
I don't want to go play. I never have.
I train in my spare time here and there,
so don't worry about it.
But...
you must want a change
of scenery sometimes.
I hear they're setting off
fireworks tonight...
so, please, go.
Right.
If you're not dizzy by then,
shall I carry you on my back
to just before the bridge?
What?
Even if you can't go today,
they'll be setting off fireworks
next year and the year after,
so we can just go then.
The only time I found nursing
to be a hassle...
was when Koyuki started sobbing
while we were talking.
I'm sure she was feeling down,
sick in bed...
but it made me uncomfortable
when she cried.
SORYU
Oh, I get it.
This is the character
for the "haku" in your name?
It's the same as the "koma" in komainu.
That makes sense.
Just as I thought, you're the same as me.
You can't get by
unless you have something to protect.
Just like those komainu,
the dogs who guard the shrines.
The reason why the master owned
all this land and the dojo...
despite not being a samurai or anything...
was because he'd rescued
an elderly man from bandits,
who, greatly moved
by his Soryu Style moves,
left him his land and dojo,
for which he had no heirs.
But that didn't sit well
with those who wanted
to have that land and dojo for themselves.
The kenjutsu dojo next door
started harassing the Soryu Dojo.
Because of that, the Soryu Dojo
couldn't get any new students.
But thanks to my training there...
and my caring for Koyuki...
my heart found salvation.
Three years went by...
and I turned 18.
Koyuki was 16.
She was almost never bedridden anymore...
and could now live a normal life.
Hakuji...
Got a second?
Sure!
So...
will you take over this dojo
for me, Hakuji?
Koyuki says she likes you, too.
Huh?
My future as someone
with the tattoos of a criminal...
wasn't something that I could picture.
Much less a future with someone
who feels fond of a person like me.
Could it be that, just like my dad said...
I would be able to lead
an honest life now?
The faint hope
of starting all over in life...
began to swell uncontrollably.
At that moment...
I had no inkling that the two people
I wanted to protect with my life...
would be poisoned to death.
I went to Edo to visit my dad's grave.
I wanted to let him know
that I was getting married.
Though I returned to the dojo
before the sun went down...
I felt nauseous even before
I heard about it.
My diaphragm seized up...
and I had goosebumps
from an ominous premonition.
Someone put poison in the well!
Because they could never beat you
or Mr. Keizo head-on...
they did this horrible thing!
Atrocious! It's unthinkable!
They even killed Koyuki!
When my loved ones
find themselves in danger...
I'm never nearby.
Even though I'd promised her...
Are you sure you're fine with me?
Do you remember when we were children,
and we talked about seeing the fireworks?
Huh? No...
Uh...
Thanks to those little chats we had,
Mr. Hakuji, I felt joy many times.
You said that even if we couldn't see
the fireworks this year...
we could just go next year
or the year after that.
I could never imagine a future
in which I'd still be alive
next year or the year after that.
Neither could my mother.
I think that's why she killed herself...
because she didn't want to see me die.
I could tell that my father
had given up, too, deep down inside.
Because I was so weak.
But you were able
to see my future, Mr. Hakuji.
You talked about next year and the year
after that as if it were perfectly normal.
That really made me happy!
You're the one for me, Mr. Hakuji.
Will you...
be my husband?
Yes.
I'm going to become stronger
than anyone else...
and protect you for the rest of my life.
In the end...
it was all talk, and I was never able
to see a single thing through to the end.
What do you want?
How impolite!
You bastard...
from Soryu!
After the father
and daughter of the Soryu Dojo
were murdered by poison,
one of the surviving students
attacked the neighboring kenjutsu dojo...
killing 67 people!
He shattered their skulls and crushed
their organs with his bare hands!
Not only did he smash and mangle
most of the bodies beyond recognition,
they're all missing a significant
amount of body parts!
The walls and ceilings are strewn
with jaws, brains and eyeballs...
as well as limbs and organs,
making for a hellish sight!
The murderer was no ordinary human!
So, I hear a huge commotion
about a demon sighting
where I never sent one.
And now that I've come
to see for myself...
I find that it was a mere human.
What a letdown.
Move it.
I'll kill you!
I'm thinking of creating
around 12 powerful demons.
I wonder if you can withstand
the amount of blood I'm going to give you.
Don't...
care anymore...
about anything...
After turning into a demon,
I lost my memories...
and once again, I began to seek power!
More!
Show me more of what you've got!
Even though I no longer...
had a single thing left
that I wanted to protect.
Even though it wasn't
as if I wanted to live in a world...
without my family.
For over a century, I committed
senseless massacres over and over.
What an absolutely pathetic, absurd...
and worthless past.
Even if I die, I can't go
where the other three are.
Damn you for making me remember...
that past of mine!
Damn humans!
Such delicate, fragile weaklings!
They die too easily!
They break!
They vanish into thin air!
He's still not dead!
Unbelievable!
I have to kill him right now!
If we let him regenerate now,
we're done for!
I blacked out!
In the middle of the battle!
His head!
His head's starting to regenerate!
But I chopped it off!
Destructive Death, Annihilation Type!
Stop it!
That kid! He can still move?
I'll behead you as many times as it takes!
We're going to win!
Mr. Giyu and I together!
We're beating Akaza!
My sword!
It slipped out of his hands!
My grip!
Time to be reborn...
young man.
I despise weaklings!
Weaklings...
They pour poison into a well...
instead of fighting fair and square!
They're atrocious!
The weak have no patience!
They get desperate too soon!
I killed people with my fists
meant for protection!
I sullied my master's
beloved Soryu with blood...
and I couldn't follow
my dad's last wishes!
That's right.
The one I wanted to kill...
Not good! Not good! Not good!
My sword flew off somewhere!
I can't stop him just by punching him!
Akaza's about to unleash
the Annihilation Type move
that he used on Mr. Rengoku!
I have to take Mr. Giyu with me
out of the attack range!
Forget about me!
I've got to kill them.
The weakling...
that I hate so much!
He attacked himself.
Why would he turn on himself like that?
Why?
For a second...
I could pick up the scent
of gratitude from Akaza.
Why did he smile?
That's enough! Stop it!
Don't regenerate!
The battle is over!
I lost!
I lost decisively in that moment!
That was a clean, splendid technique!
You anticipated
the enemy's movements to perfection,
pivoted at the last second...
and struck before the enemy had finished
unleashing his move!
It's over now.
I want to accept my fate...
and go to Hell.
Where does he want to go?
He stopped in his tracks.
Dad...
Are you all right now?
You're not in any pain?
I'm fine, Hakuji.
Thank you, Son.
Sorry, Dad.
Sorry I couldn't start over.
It didn't work out.
It doesn't matter.
No matter how you turn out,
you're my son and student.
We won't desert you even in death!
Though we can't take you
with us to Heaven.
Master...
Didn't you want to become stronger?
Is this it for you...
Akaza?
That's right.
I'm going to get stronger.
I want to become stronger!
So, what if I got beheaded?
Win? Lose? Who cares?
I'm going to kill 'em all!
I can still become stronger!
I have to keep my promise!
Mr. Hakuji...
Thank you.
That's enough.
That's enough now.
It's all right.
Akaza!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry I couldn't protect you!
I'm sorry I wasn't there
when it counted the most!
I couldn't keep a single promise I made!
Forgive me!
I'm begging you, please forgive me!
I'm so glad...
that you remembered us.
I'm so glad that you're back
to being the Mr. Hakuji that I know!
Welcome home, Hakuji.
Hey, Hakuji!
Welcome home!
I'm home.
I'm back now.
Welcome home...
my darling!
Hey...
He vanished.
It's... over.
Gotta hurry.
We've got to...
go to Ms. Tamayo...
next...
Tanjiro!
Tanjiro, Giyu...
have defeated Upper Three!
They are unable to stay conscious
due to exhaustion!
They've passed out!
Tanjiro, Giyu...
have defeated Upper Three!
Upper Three!
Akaza's...
presence is gone.
Who knew that he'd lose?
Akaza!
Weren't you going to defeat me?
Who knew that you'd willingly abandon...
the path you opened to greater heights?
How absurdly weak!
Could...
Lord Akaza...
possibly be d-dead?
I felt a weird presence for a moment,
but it was just my imagination, right?
Like Lord Akaza...
had turned into some other creature.
Well, now that he's dead, I have no clue!
Let's see.
Where was I?
Oh, right, I remember!
I'd asked you your name, right?
Tanjiro, Giyu...
have defeated Upper Three!
Upper Three!
Mr. Himejima!
Yes.
Good job, Tomioka!
Good job, Kamado!
That's amazing,
Mr. Tomioka, Tanjiro!
We're going to follow their lead.
Right!
Don't die, Agatsuma!
If you don't hurry it up, I'll poke you!
Listen up!
Show me where the strongest demon is!
Got that?
Comin' through!
This way! This way!
There's a powerful
guy over here!
Where's Big Brother?
Bring me
an Upper Rank!
An Upper Rank!
Hey!
Stop running
from me!
The passageway
leading north...
on the 88th level...
no sign of Muzan.
The 100th...
and 27th levels in
the southeast...
no sign of Muzan.
Where?
Where is he?
Where could he be?
No sign of Muzan...
on any of the levels
from 90 to 100, either.
Covering the entire
100th and 33rd levels.
No sign of Muzan.
Our crows'll find
you without fail!
We're going
over this castle...
with a fine-tooth
comb, and...
we'll track you down
wherever you go!
FOUR
Multi-layered structures are
now moving to the northeast.
New structures
are moving...
vertically and
horizontally!
Folding over themselves!
- And becoming one!
Who would've thought...
No...
we don't have the option
to lose.
Crows, go on!
To where Muzan is!
Those eyesore
Demon Slayers!
You'll never be able
to reach me!
You may be
feeling smug...
about beheading
an Upper Rank...
but unless
you kill me...
it means nothing!
You're going to die meaninglessly
without ever seeing my face!
So fitting for you foolish,
meaningless lot!
When I'm done here...
I'm going to make you regret
that you were ever alive!
You're going to struggle, suffer
and writhe around in pain!
And for you Demon Slayers...
this will be your final night...
the day of your death!
Don't die!
Giyu!
Tanjiro, don't you die on us!
Downloaded from MoviesMod.at